<cookingBook>
    <recipe>
        <id>id_0</id>
        <name>Ultimate Chocolate Cake</name>
        <description>
            Indulge yourself with this ultimate chocolate cake recipe that is beautifully moist, rich and fudgy. 
            Perfect for a celebration or an afternoon tea.
        </description>
        <ingredients>
            200g butter, 
            3 eggs, 
            75g milk, 
            1 tbsp coffee, 
            400g dark chocolate, 
            200g sugar, 
            25g cocoa powder, 
            85g flour, 
            300g cream, 
            1/4 soda
        </ingredients>
        <instruction>
            Heat the oven to 160C. Put 200g chopped dark chocolate in a medium pan with 200g butter. 
            Mix 1 tbsp instant coffee granules into 125ml cold water and pour into the pan. 
            Warm through over a low heat just until everything is melted – don’t overheat. 
            Or melt in the microwave for about 5 minutes, stirring halfway through. 
            Mix 85g plain flour, 1/4 tsp bicarbonate of soda, 200g sugar and 25g cocoa powder, and squash out any lumps. 
            Beat 3 medium eggs with 75ml buttermilk. Pour the melted chocolate mixture and the egg mixture into the 
            flour mixture and stir everything to a smooth, quite runny consistency. Pour this into the tin and bake for 1hr 25 – 1hr 30 mins. 
            If you push a skewer into the centre it should come out clean and the top should feel firm (don’t worry if it cracks a bit). 
            Leave to cool in the tin (don’t worry if it dips slightly), then turn out onto a wire rack to cool completely. 
            Cut the cold cake horizontally into three. To make the ganache, put 200g chopped dark chocolate in a bowl. 
            Pour 300g double cream into a pan and heat until it is about to boil. Take off the heat and pour it over the chocolate. 
            Stir until the chocolate has melted and the mixture is smooth. Cool until it is a little thicker but still pourable.
            Sandwich the layers together with just a little of the ganache. Pour the rest over the cake letting it fall down the sides 
            and smooth over any gaps with a palette knife. Decorate with 50g grated chocolate or 100g chocolate curls. 
            The cake keeps moist and gooey for 3-4 days.
        </instruction>
    </recipe>
    <recipe>
        <id>id_1</id>
        <name>Homemade Chicken Soup</name>
        <description>
            Homemade chicken soup - but you don't have to be sick to deserve or enjoy it - you do, so do! Good for body and soul!
        </description>
        <ingredients>
            1 chicken, 
            4 carrots, 
            4 stalks celery, 
            1 onion, 
            1 tbsp salt, 
            1 tbsp pepper, 
            1 tsp chicken boullion
        </ingredients>
        <instruction>
            Put the chicken, carrots, celery and onion in a large soup pot and cover with cold water. 
            Heat and simmer, uncovered, until the chicken meat falls off of the bones (skim off foam every so often). 
            Take everything out of the pot. Strain the broth. Pick the meat off of the bones and chop the carrots, celery and onion. 
            Season the broth with salt, pepper and chicken bouillon to taste, if desired. 
            Return the chicken, carrots, celery and onion to the pot, stir together, and serve.
        </instruction>
    </recipe>
    <recipe>
        <id>id_2</id>
        <name>Italian Meatballs</name>
        <description>
            These are my idea of "perfect" meatballs. I make them extra soft and juicy by using bread instead of breadcrumbs, 
            and the grated onion is my secret tip for adding extra flavour into this. Plus, no need to sauté diced onion before mixing it in! 
            Served with a rich tomato sauce made extra tasty by cooking it in the same pan that the meatballs are browned in.
        </description>
        <ingredients>
            1 cup diced bread, 
            400g ground beef, 
            100g ground pork, 
            1 egg, 
            1 onion, 
            3/4 tbsp salt, 
            1/4 tbsp pepper, 
            1/4 cup parmesan, 
            2 garlic cloves, 
            1/4 cup parsley
        </ingredients>
        <instruction>
            Grate the onion using a standard box grater in a large bowl until you have about 1/2 cup of grated onion and juices. 
            Add bread, mix to combine so the onion juice soaks the bread and disintegrates. Set aside while you prep the other ingredients (5 min or so). 
            Add all the remaining Meatball ingredients. Use hands to mix well. 
            Measure out a heaped tablespoon and roll lightly to form a ball. Repeat with remaining mixture. 
            Heat 1 1/2 tbsp olive oil in a large non stick fry pan over medium high heat. Add the meatballs and brown all over - about 3 - 4 minutes. 
            When they are browned but NOT cooked through, carefully transfer them onto a plate.
        </instruction>
    </recipe>
</cookingBook>